JIN KUAN MOO

https://minahhh666.github.io/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/jin-kuan-moo/

Summary

A UCD Computer Science Master proficient in Chinese Mandarin, English, and Malay. Full stack development experience in several languages as well as **Agile** methodology. Great networking (TCP/IP), distributed systems, database, OS, container, and cloud knowledge. Currently working as a freelance web designer and frontend developer. Previously worked as a manager, leading a team of 20 engaged in daily production. Volunteered in Code in Place hosted by Stanford University, delivering online Python lessons to a group of 15 students. Have more than 3 years of investing and trading experience with decent financial knowledge.

Email: jkmoo0412@hotmail.com

Mobile: 0892059402

Education

University College Dublin Dublin, Ireland MSc Computer Science; GPA:3.82 (First Class Honours) Sep 2022 – Dec 2023

Cornell University New York, United States Exchange Programme; GPA:3.87 (First Class Honours) Aug 2019 – Dec 2019

University College Dublin Dublin, Ireland BSc Food Science; GPA:3.77 (First Class Honours) Sep 2017 – Jun 2021

Experience

Freelancer Dublin, Ireland Sep 2023 – Now

Web designer/Frontend developer

• Designing personal/commercial website for customers

Experience in WordPress, Domain & Email Hosting, HTML/CSS, JavaScript

Stanford University Dublin, Ireland Python Tutor Apr 2023 – Jun 2023

• Participating in Code in Place, an online introductory coding course

• Conducting weekly lessons for a cohort of 15 students

• Teaching topics including Python, Animations, Console Programming, Graphic Programming etc.

Krispy Kreme Kildare, Ireland Manufacturing Manager Sep 2021 – Jun 2022

- Managing a 20-member team for daily production operations
- Ensuring adherence to safety protocols, HACCP principles, and legal regulations
- Maintaining accurate inventory control, yield records, and traceability documents

Projects

Afterparty (Backend Developer)

an event impact analysis tool which provides insights into how the busyness of urban areas are impacted by largescale event.

- Utilized React.js, Mapbox GL.js, and Figma for the frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Node.js, Express.js, Flask, and Apache
- Developed prediction models using Random Forest and XGBoost

Dublin Bikes (Full-Stack Developer)

a web application providing real-time information and journey planning for bike-sharing services.

- Utilized Vanilla JS, HTML, CSS, and Google Maps API for frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Flask, MySQL, AWS EC2, AWS RDS, Gunicorn, Nginx
- Developed prediction models using Linear Regression

Asteroids (Frontend Developer)

a classic arcade video game which player controls a spaceship in an asteroid field to destroy incoming asteroids.

- Developed using Java
- Used JavaFX as the GUI framework

Technical Skills

- Programming languages: Python, JavaScript, Java, Ruby, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, Object-oriented, Bash, Astra
- Frameworks: React.js, Flask, Express.js, JavaFX, Pygame
- Database: MySQL, AWS RDS, NoSQL, MongoDB
- OS: Linux, Windows
- Tools: Jupyter Notebook , Microsoft Office, WordPress
- DevOps: Jenkins, GitHub, Unit Testing, Apache Maven
- Cloud: AWS, GCP, Docker, Kubernetes
- Distributed Systems: MapReduce, Hadoop, Spark, Rest, RMI, Middleware, Web Services
- Machine Learning: Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, Random Forest, XGBoost, KNN, Scikit-learn
- Others: Data Structures and Algorithms, Networking (TCP/IP)

Honours

- UCD Global Southeast Excellent Scholarship
- UCD Food Science Scholarship
- Kepak Best in Class Award